# Mukhammadzhon Khakimov

# Frontend Developer

Last update: November 27, 2022

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

https://Muhammadzhon.github.io/muhammad-bio

Russian

SPA

Residence		♠ Osh, Kyrgyzstan				
Linkedin		in <u>Mukhammadzhon</u>				
GitHub		Muhammadzhon				
Phone		<u>+996 (555) 00 43 45</u>				
Email		$\triangleright$	<u>hmuhamm</u>	<u>adjon</u>		
HTML	CSS	••••	JavaScript	••••		

I'm a self study frontend developer. The purpose for my last 5 years search happens to find the job which I love. And I realized only web developing going to fill my life path! After HTML CSS and JS learning React makes me confident and ambitions.

Turkish

Github

# **Professional Experience**

02/2021 - 10/2022

English

React

#### Dispatcher

Bilato holding takes leading position on delivering freight over USA and services 24/7 over 200 trucks and truck dri

As a dispatcher I'm responsible for:

- \* Scheduling truck drivers time and route
- $\ast$  Monitoring pick-up, transit and drop off process of the loads
- \* Solving unexpected issues
- \* Quick response for drivers requests

Fluent English	Russian	Turkish	Communication	Customer service	Team work

03/2017 - 01/2021

### Sales Manager

Mukum Auto has history in auto market over 20 years

Responsibilities:

- \* Searching cars for purchase
- st Diognosing and repairing
- \* Preparing for Sales
- $\ \ \ast$  Dealing with potential buyers face to face and over phone

Analytical skills	Customer service	Detailing	product delivery

### **Education**

International Kazak-Turkish Ahmet Yesevi University [2011 - 2016]